Thank you for watching!
Yes, hi, this is Ruff Ruff YouTube.
This is Ruff Ruff.
Wait a minute.
I'm a YouTuber with 1.27 million subscribers.
Don't laugh.
I'm on YouTube with this granddad.
Come on!
Start!
(laughter)
And here they are this time.
Funny, funny, funny.
Everyone is funny.
To us like comedy.
Laughing.
Seen, love love love.
Please give my best regards.
Good. Take care, everybody.
What's up with this?
I'm sorry.
Your eyes are all misty.
Okay, let's take a look at the pre-recording.
Let's have him come in here for a minute.
Masaki, how's the radio?
Can I take a few shots?
(laughs)
You okay?
What's up with the radio?
I fell asleep today.
Yeah, I know.
I fell asleep.
I joined in for a bit at the end.
To the person who fell asleep, Hibino-san.
I'm calling remotely.
I was asked something like, "Hibino-san, are you awake? He was like, "Hibino-san, are you awake?
(laughter)
I did it.
(laughter)LOL!
I did my best.
Laughter
It's okay.
Who made everyone's biggest heart?
Ah~~
I'm not your best friend.
What's up with the radio? I just heard it.
You told him to die.
I knew that, I just listened.
Ah~~.
Yes, I did. That's why.
I gave the order, didn't I?
Ah~.
God's turn to edit.
No, it's not. It's not a variety show. Not here.
If it was a variety party, the hotel would be there.
Not this time,
Actually, I got a message from one of the staff.
A message to my old self.
A message to my future self.
A message for the future, or a thought for the members.
and your thoughts about the members?
Yes, I do. I listened to it.
I didn't know what it was for.
It was for the second one-one.
Yes.
How do you think it will be used?
I think it will be used in a very moving way.
I think it will be played in the opening.
Yes. What about the rest?
It's a very moving song, so I think it will be played at the opening.
After making everyone cry.
I won't allow you to do it.
I won't forgive you.I won't allow it.
Well? Well then, Nagamatsu.
I'm going to fold it into a contraption.
I see.
Fujisaka.
I'll play it at the opening.
The third time already.
The third time.
I don't know what it will be used for.
I don't know if you know yet.
Actually, it's a song.
It's a song.
What?
Let's hand over the rental card, please.
What? What do you mean?
A letter?
Thank you very much.
Is everything okay?
What I mean is that we tried to mix letters to our old selves written by all the members into the lyrics of the song,
We decided to write a song that we would send to ourselves when we sang it,
What? What are you going to do?
Well, you see, if we tried to actually write the lyrics, we would probably get stuck on our shoulders and try to look cool,
So I wrote a song called "Letter to My Old Self," and I put the message I got in the lyrics.
So, I wrote a song called "Letter to My Old Self.
Wow!
Your lyrics.
Let's listen to the borrowed song.
ungef wow ors
zar
Do you remember me from that day?
This thought that I can say now
I was longing for
I'm drawing the rest of the lyrics
I'm drawing
It's okay to cry
Beyond the tears
There are these lyrics, aren't there?You have these lyrics.
Someday I'll know something wonderful
That time and now are connected
Nibai-sen, let's always go straight ahead
Be myself, the future I longed for
Believe in Be myself
Enter Rett
wh
Limaisense Someday, with these wonderful feet
In her bird, we'll be connected
Someday I'll go straight ahead
Be myself, just like I've always wanted to be
Make it happen
Yes, that was the song!
So, you wrote a wonderful song for us,
Also, the lyricist did a great job putting all of your letters together.
Do you have any of Saito's lyrics as a result?
Yes, I didn't expect it to be lyrics,
But when I listened to it, I was so moved even though I hadn't sung it yet,
I feel like I'm going to cry at the concert.
I don't know what to do, I'm worried.
When I look at the part where it is written like a sentence written by someone else,
I see that there are some overlaps between the members,
I felt that we are all welcoming this moment with the same feelings,
I think this is a song that I want to sing no matter how many years pass.
But you know, we start recording right after practicing,
Please make sure that the song conveys your feelings to as many people as possible.
So, we will be recording songs such as letters from the members, Lehmeiself, and others,
Rough Rough's second one-man live will be full of new songs,
We hope you will come and enjoy it.
Congratulations!
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you very much.
In
at
the
of
yo!(in mid-sentence) used to catch one's breath
along the way
Chinese "rooftop" constellation (one of the 28 mansions)
please
Please do so.